Batoul Al-ibraheem

■ batoulab268@gmail.com

+963 932 763 995

Date of birth 10 Sep 2000

Nationality Syrian

Address Banias, Tartous, Syria

LinkedIn linkedIn linkedIn linkedin.com/in/batoul-alibraheem/

GitHub Batoul7

PERSONAL PROFILE

A software engineer specializing in front-end development, with extensive experience in designing and building user interfaces using React. Strong skills in transforming creative ideas into interactive web applications enhance the user experience. Experience across various projects has fostered an understanding of customer needs and the ability to translate them into effective technical solutions. Committed to staying up to date with the latest trends and technologies, with a strong belief in the importance of collaboration and teamwork. A creative and dedicated front-end developer ready to add real value to any team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Next Js
- Redux
- React JS
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Rest Api

- WebSocket-Real time Api
- HTML 5 / CSS 3
- Git GitHub

Sass

- C++ / Java
- From Figma to Code
- OOP

PROJECTS

Focal X.

1) Blog (GitHub: task6-blog | Live Demo: task6-blog/)

Description: Blog using React, Redux and Tailwind during my training at Focal X.

- 2) Products site (GitHub: task5-crud)
 - **Description:** A site that displays products and can be viewed, edited and deleted using Rest Api and crud operations during my training at Focal X.
- 3) Landing page (GitHub: <u>task4-medicio</u> | Live Demo: <u>task4-medicio/</u>)
 Description: Landing page design for medicio website using bootstrap and react during my training at
- 4) Landing page (GitHub: <u>task3-villa</u> | Live Demo: <u>task3-villa/</u>)

 Description: Landing page design for villas website using react during my training at Focal X.
- 5) Dashboard (GitHub: React-Dashboard)

Description: Create a dashboard using: front-end (React), back-end (Laravel).

6) Design 3 template:

(**GitHub:** Kasper <u>template-kasper</u> - Elzero <u>Template-Elzero</u> - Dashboard <u>React-Dashboard</u>)

Description: using only html and css.

EXPERIENCE

1/8/2024 - Present

Intern at Focal X agency as a Front-End Developer (React)

2022 - Present

Experience in designing and developing websites (Front-end) using Html, Css, Javascript and React.

EDUCATION

15/7/2024 - Present

Master in Web Science (MWS)

Studying at the Syrian Virtual University

2019 - 2023

Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering (IT)

Major: Software Engineer

Tishreen University, Latakia, Syria

• Achievement: Graduation from the College of Informatics Engineering with a very good graduation rate 78.73%

PERSONAL SKILLS

Job-related skills

- Ability to work within a team
- Ability to communicate effectively
- Strong will to learn and grow

Core skills

- Strong written and verbal communication skills in English
- Positive attitude
- Articulate, Organized, and goal-oriented with excellent presentation skills
- Ability to work independently in a fast-paced environment

LANGUEGE

Arabic: Native proficiency English: Middle (B2 level)